
{
    "results": [
     
      {
            "question": "4, 9, 25, 49, 121, ______  ",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 144",
                "b. 196",
                "d. 100"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c. 169",
        "explanation:"2^2=4, 3^2=9, 5^2=25, 7^2=49, 11^2=121, 13^2=169"
        },
 {
            "question": "48, 120, 168, 288, 360, ________ ",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 516",
                "c. 384",
                "d. 624"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 528",
        "explanation:"7^2-1=48, 11^2-1=120, 13^2-1=168, 17^2-1=288, 19^2-1=360, 23^2-1=528 "
        },

         {
            "question": "11, 41, 88, 155, 238, _______ ",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 329",
                "c. 386",
                "d. 385"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 341",
        "explanation:"3^2+3=12, 6^2+5=41, 9^2+7=88, 12^2+11=155, 15^2+13=238, 18^2+17=341"
        },

         {
            "question": "4, 11, 22, 45, 66, ______ ",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 82",
                "b. 95",
                "c. 134"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d. 103",
        "explanation:"3x1+1=4, 5x2+1=11, 7x3+1=22, 11x4+1=45, 13x5+1=66, 17x6+1=103"
        },

         {
            "question": "81, 72, 72 63, 63, 63, ______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 72",
                "b. 61",
                "d. 63"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c. 54",
        "explanation:"97-(9+7)=81, 89-(8+9)=72, 83-(8+3)=72, 79-(7+9)=63, 73-(7+3)=63, 71-(7+1)=63, 67-(6+7)=54"
        },

         {
            "question": "112,100,76,64,40,28,_______ ",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 18",
                "b. 16",
                "d. 63"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 16",
        "explanation:"19x6-2=112, 17x6-2=100, 13x6-2=76, 11x6-2=64, 7x6-2=40, 5x6-
2=28, 3x6-2=16"
        },
 {
            "question": "5, 8, 17, 24, 37, ________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 46",
                "b. 44",
                "d. 45"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c. 48",
        "explanation:"2^2+1=5, 3^2-1=8, 4^2+1=17, 5^2-1=24, 6^2+1=37, 7^2-1=48"
        },

         {
            "question": "8, 9, 125, 49, 1331, _______ ",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 2197",
                "c. 225",
                "d. 144"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 169",
        "explanation:"2^3=8, 3^2=9, 5^3=125, 7^2=49, 11^3=1331, 13^2=169"
        },

         {
            "question": "14, 22, 26, 34, 38, ________ ",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 44",
                "c. 48",
                "d. 42"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 46",
        "explanation:" 7x2=14, 11x2=22, 13x2=26, 17x2=34, 19x2=38, 23x2=46"
        },

         {
            "question": "3, 11, 17, 21, 27, ______ ",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 27",
                "c. 33",
                "d. 31"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 29",
        "explanation:"100-97=3,100-89=11, 100-83=17, 100-79=21,100-73=27,100-71=29"
        },

         {
            "question": "2, 20, 46, 80, 122, _____",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b.152",
                "c.170",
                "d.168"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a.172",
        "explanation:"Difference of number series follows +8 difference"
        },

         {
            "question": "900, 648, 448, 294, _____",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a.190",
                "c.274",
                "d.186"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b.180",
        "explanation:"10^3-10^2=900, 9^3-9^2=648, 8^3-8^2=448, 7^3-7^2=294, 6^3-6^2=180"
        },

         {
            "question": "27, 32, 30, 35, 33, _____",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a.32",
                "b.33",
                "c.31"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d.38",
        "explanation:"27+5=32, 32-2=30, 30+5=35, 35-2=33, 33+5=38"
        },

         {
            "question": "3, 5, 9, 17, 33, 65, _____",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a.116",
                "b.128",
                "c.112"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d.129",
        "explanation:"2^1+1=3, 2^2+1=5, 2^3+1=9, 2^4+1=17, 2^5+1=33, 2^6+1=65, 2^7+1=129"
        },

         {
            "question": "5, 24, 63, 128, 225, 360, _____",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b.296",
                "c.425",
                "d.469"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a.539",
        "explanation:"5*1^2=5, 6*2^2=24, 7*3^2=63, 8*4^2=128, 9*5^2=225, 10*6^2=360, 11*7^2=539"
        },

         {
            "question": "1, 5, 11, 19, 29, 41, _____",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a.49",
                "b.55",
                "c.47"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d.53",
        "explanation:"0*1+1=1, 1*2+3=5, 2*3+5=11, 3*4+7=19, 4*5+9=29, 5*6+11=41, 6*7+13=55 "
        },

         {
            "question": "12, 36, 80, 150, 252, 392, _____",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a.512",
                "b.249",
                "c.481"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d.576",
        "explanation:"2^2+2^3=12, 3^2+3^3=36, 4^2+4^3=80, 5^2+5^3=150, 6^2+6^3=252, 7^2+7^3=392, 8^2+8^3=576"
        },

         {
            "question": "9, 14, 16, 20, 22, _____",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a.24",
                "c.20",
                "d.28"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b.26",
        "explanation:"9+5=14, 9+7=16, 9+11=20, 9+13=22, 9+17=26"
        },

         {
            "question": "98, 103, 95, 107, 89, _____",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a.114",
                "b.112",
                "d.111"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c.113",
        "explanation:"100-2=98, 100+3=103, 100-5=95, 100+7=107, 100-11=89, 100+13=113"
        },

         {
            "question": "50, 41, 33, 26, 20, 15, _____",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b.12",
                "c.13",
                "d.14"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a.11",
        "explanation:"50-9=41, 41-8=33, 33-7=26, 26-6=20, 20-5=15, 15-4=11"
        },

         {
            "question": "8, 14, 26, 50, 98, _______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 184",
                "c. 176",
                "d. 204"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 194",
        "explanation:" 8+6=14, 14+12=26, 26+24=50, 50+48=98, 98+96=194"
        },

         {
            "question": "989, 978, 967, 956, 945, _______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 914",
                "c. 926",
                "d. 936"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 934",
        "explanation:"1000-11=989, 1000-22=978, 1000-33=967, 1000-44=956, 1000-55=945, 1000-66=934"
        },

         {
            "question": "9, 15, 27, 51, 99, ________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 198",
                "c. 193",
                "d. 202"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 195",
        "explanation:"double each fig and subtract 3
 9×2-3=15, 15×2-3=27, 27×2-3=51, 51×2-3=99, 99×2-3=195"
        },

         {
            "question": "6, 21, 52, 105, 186, _______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 241",
                "b. 236",
                "c. 201"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d. 301",
        "explanation:"2^3-2×1=6, 3^3-3×2=21, 4^3-4×3=52, 5^3-5×4=105, 6^3-6×5=186, 7^3-7×6=301"
        },

         {
            "question": "23, 55, 109, 191, 307, ______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 473",
                "c. 403",
                "d. 389"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 463",
        "explanation:"3^3-2^2=23, 4^3-3^2=55, 5^3-4^2=109, 6^3-5^2=191, 7^3-6^2=307, 8^3-7^2=463"
        },

         {
            "question": "1729, 1632, 1640, 1646, 1650, ______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 1648",
                "c. 1658",
                "d. 1654"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 1656",
        "explanation:"1729-97=1632, 1729-89=1640, 1729-83=1646, 1729-79=1650, 1729-73=1656"
        },

         {
            "question": "97, 92, 85, 76, 65, _______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 64",
                "b. 54",
                "c. 48"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d. 52",
        "explanation:"(100-2^2)+1=97, (100-3^2)+1=92, (100-4^2)+1=85, (100-5^2)+1=76, (100-6^2)+1=65, (100-7^2)+1=52"
        },

         {
            "question": "97, 16, 89, 17, 83, 11, 79, ______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 17",
                "c. 13",
                "d. 11"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 16",
        "explanation:"9+7=16, 8+9=17, 8+3=11, 7+9=16"
        },

         {
            "question": "15, 35, 143, 323, ________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 878",
                "c. 749",
                "d. 829"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 899",
        "explanation:"Product of twin prime numbers 29×31=899"
        },

         {
            "question": "5, 8, 40, 320, 12800, ________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 40960",
                "b. 408600",
                "d. 40980"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c. 4096000",
        "explanation:"5×8=40, 8×40=320, 40×320=12800, 320×12800=4096000"
        },

         {
            "question": "18, 27, 36, 63, 72, ___________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "(b) 79",
                "(c) 90",
                "(d) 82"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "(a) 81",
        "explanation:"1+8=9, 2+7=9, 3+6=9, and reverse 6+3=9, 7+2=9, 8+1=9, Answer - 81 "
        },

         {
            "question": "1, 10, 27, 52, 85, ___________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "(b) 124",
                "(c) 121",
                "(d) 144"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "(a) 126",
        "explanation:"1^2+0=1, 3^2+1=10, 5^2+2=27, 7^2+3=52, 9^2+4=85, 11^2+5=126"
        },

         {
            "question": "882, 776, 672, 570, 470, ___________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "(a) 721",
                "(b) 425",
                "(d) 384"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "(c) 372",
        "explanation:"99*9-9=882, 98*8-8=776, 97*7-7=672, 96*6-6=570, 95*5-5=470, 94*4-4=372"
        },

         {
            "question": "98, 12, 87, 23, 76, 34, 65, ___________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "(b) 63",
                "(c) 54",
                "(d) 72"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "(a) 45",
        "explanation:"Series I - 11*9-1, 11*8-1, 11*7-1, 11*6-1 ---- 98,87,76,65
 Series II - 11*1+1, 11*2+1, 11*3+1, 11*4+1 ---- 12,23,34,45"
        },

         {
            "question": "11, 31, 69, 131, 223, ___________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "(a) 341",
                "(c) 296",
                "(d) 310"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "(b) 351",
        "explanation:"2^3+3=11, 3^3+4=31, 4^3+5=69, 5^3+6=131, 6^3+7=223, 7^3+8=351"
        },

         {
            "question": "4, 9, 25, 49, 121, 169, 289, ___________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "(a) 341",
                "(b) 351",
                "(c) 391"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "(d) 361",
        "explanation:"Prime numbers squares. "
        },

         {
            "question": "5, 10, 17, 26, 37, ___________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "(a) 49",
                "(c) 48",
                "(d) 56"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "(b) 50",
        "explanation:"1*2+3 = 5, 2*3+4=10, 3*4+5=17, 4*5+6=26, 5*6+7=37, 6*7+8=50"
        },

         {
            "question": "99, 96, 91, 84, 75, 64, 51, ___________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "(a) 38",
                "(b) 32",
                "(d) 30"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "(c) 36",
        "explanation:"100-1=99, 100-4=96, 100-9=91, 100-16=84, 100-25=75, 100-36=64, 100-49=51, 100-64=36"
        },

         {
            "question": "24, 36, 58, 79, 1110, 1312 ___________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "(b) 1713",
                "(c) 1711",
                "(d) 1715"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "(a) 1714",
        "explanation:"(a) Prime number composite number
 (Excluding the number) it self"
        },

         {
            "question": "6, 6, 20, 20, 42, 42, ___________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "(a) 68",
                "(c) 76",
                "(d) 78"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "(b) 72",
        "explanation:"2*2+2=6, 3*3-3=6, 4*4+4=20, 5*5-5=20, 6*6+6=42, 7*7-7=42, 8*8+8=72"
        },

         {
            "question": "4096, 3375, 2740, 2197, 1728, 1331",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 3375",
                "c. 2197",
                "d. 1331"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 2740",
        "explanation:"16^3=4096, 15^3=3375, 14^3=2744, 13^3=2197, 12^3=1728, 11^3=1331"
        },

         {
            "question": "288,168,121,48,24,8,3",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 168",
                "b. 48",
                "c. 24"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d. 121",
        "explanation:"17^2-1=288, 13^2-1=168, 11^2-1=120, 7^2-1=48, 5^2-1=24, 3^2-1=8, 2^2-1=3"
        },

         {
            "question": "10, 34, 84,144, 230, 318",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 318",
                "b. 230",
                "d. 34"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c. 144",
        "explanation:"3^2+1=10, 6^2-2=34, 9^2+3=84, 12^2-4=140, 15^2+5=230, 18^2-6=318"
        },

         {
            "question": "2, 6, 12, 20, 36, 42, 56",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a.12",
                "c.56",
                "d.42"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b.36",
        "explanation:"1^2+1=2, 2^2+2=6, 3^2+3=12, 4^2+4=20, 5^2+5=30, 6^2+6=42, 7^2+7=56"
        },

         {
            "question": "3, 15, 35, 65, 99, 143, 195",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 35",
                "c. 99",
                "d. 195"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 65",
        "explanation:"1x3=3, 3x5=15, 5x7=35, 7x9=63, 9x11=99, 11x13=143, 13x15=195"
        },

         {
            "question": "7, 13, 20, 27, 35, 43, 52, 59",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 13",
                "b. 27",
                "d. 52"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c. 35",
        "explanation:"5+2=7, 10+3=13, 15+5=20, 20+7=27, 25+11=36, 30+13=43, 35+17=52, 40+19=59"
        },

         {
            "question": "2, 8, 18, 32, 54, 72, 98",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 72",
                "c. 98",
                "d. 18"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 54",
        "explanation:"1x2=2, 4x2=8, 9x2=18, 16x2=32, 25x2=50, 36x2=72, 49x2=98"
        },

         {
            "question": "486.7, 48.77, 4.977, 0.5977, 0.15977, 0.25977",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 0.15977",
                "b.0.5977",
                "d. 48.77"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c. 0.25977",
        "explanation:"(486.7+1)/10=48.77, (48.77+1)/10=4.977, (4.977+1)/10=0.5977, (0.5977+1)/10=0.15977, (0.15977+1)/10=0.115977"
        },

         {
            "question": "64, 74, 94, 124, 164, 204, 274, 344",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 94",
                "b. 164",
                "d. 344"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c. 204",
        "explanation:"64+10=74, 74+20=94, 94+30=124, 124+40=164, 164+50=214, 214+60=274, 274+70=344 "
        },

         {
            "question": "10, 15, 25, 35, 50, 65, 85, 95",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a.15",
                "c. 85",
                "d. 95"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 50",
        "explanation:"2x5=10, 3x5=15, 5x5=25, 7x5=35, 11x5=55, 13x5=65, 17x5=85, 19x5=95 "
        },

         {
            "question": "8.9, 5.8, 2.7, ____,-3.5,-6.6",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a) -0.3",
                "b) -0.6",
                "d) -0.8"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c) -0.4",
        "explanation:"8.9-3.1=5.8, 5.8-3.1=2.7, 2.7-3.1=-0.4, -0.4-3.1=-3.5, -3.5-3.1=-6.6"
        },

         {
            "question": "1, 3, 10, ___, 39, 61",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b) 32",
                "c) 17",
                "d) 27"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a) 22",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "10, 15, 21, 28, 36, ___, 55",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a) 43",
                "c) 48",
                "d) 50"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b) 45",
        "explanation:"Triangle numbers from 10,15,21,28,36,45,55"
        },

         {
            "question": "4, 16, 36, 64, 100, ____",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a) 121",
                "b) 169",
                "d) 81"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c) 144",
        "explanation:"2^2, 4^2, 6^2, 8^2, 10^2, 12^2"
        },

         {
            "question": "2, 9, 64, 625, ____",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b) 7896",
                "c) 5496",
                "d) 4969"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a) 7776",
        "explanation:"2^1, 3^2, 4^3, 5^4, 6^5"
        },

         {
            "question": "2, 3, 12, 18, 72, ____, 432",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a) 106",
                "b) 122",
                "c) 110"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d) 108",
        "explanation:"Series I - 2*6=12, 12*6=72, 72*6=432
 Series II - 3*6=18, 18*6=108 "
        },

         {
            "question": "11, 12, 17, 24, 33, ____, 57, 72",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a) 42",
                "b) 40",
                "c) 46"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d) 44",
        "explanation:"11+1^2=12, 13+2^2=17, 15+3^2=24
     17+4^2=33, 19+5^2=44, 21+6^2=57, 23+7^2=72"
        },

         {
            "question": "81, 72, 72, 63, 63, ____, 54",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a) 72",
                "b) 63",
                "d) 57"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c) 54",
        "explanation:"97-(9+7)=81, 89-(8+9)=72, 83-(8+3)=72, 79-(7+9)=63, 73-(7+3)=63, 71-(7+1)=63, 67-(6+7)=54"
        },

         {
            "question": "6, 21, 52, ____, 186,301",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b) 101",
                "c) 98",
                "d) 112"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a) 105",
        "explanation:"2^2*1+2=6, 3^2*2+3=21, 4^2*3+4=52, 5^2*4+5=105, 6^2*5+6=186, 7^2*6+7=301"
        },

         {
            "question": "41, 43, 47, 53, 59, ____",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a) 63",
                "b) 71",
                "d) 67"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c) 61",
        "explanation:" Prime numbers from 41 "
        },

         {
            "question": "8000, 6859, ________4913, 4096, 3375",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 5824",
                "c. 5852",
                "d. 5812"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 5832",
        "explanation:"20^3, 19^3, 18^3, 17^3, 16^3, 15^3"
        },

         {
            "question": "45, 54, 63, 36, 49, 94, 83,_______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 36",
                "c.81",
                "d. 64"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 38",
        "explanation:" Reverse the digits of previous number"
        },

         {
            "question": "2, 10, 37, 101, 226,______,785",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 498",
                "c. 464",
                "d. 396"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 442",
        "explanation:"1+1^3=2, 2+2^3=10, 10+3^3=37, 37+4^3=101, 101+5^3=226, 226+6^3=442, 442+7^3=785"
        },

         {
            "question": "11, 12, 15, 16, 19, 20, 23,__________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 32",
                "b. 26",
                "c. 22"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d. 24",
        "explanation:"Series I =>11, 11+4, 15+4, 19+4, => 11,15,19,23
 Series II => 12, 12+4, 16+4, 20+4, => 12,16,20,24 "
        },

         {
            "question": "0, 2, 6, 12, 20,________42",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 28",
                "b. 27",
                "d. 25"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c. 30",
        "explanation:"1^2-1=0, 2^2-2=2, 3^2-3=6, 4^2-4=12, 5^2-5=20, 6^2-6=30, 7^2-7=42"
        },

         {
            "question": "7, 13, 21, 31, 43,__________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 62",
                "c. 49",
                "d. 54"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 57",
        "explanation:"2^2+3=7, 3^2+4=13, 4^2+5=21, 5^2+6=31, 6^2+7=43, 7^2+8=57"
        },

         {
            "question": "10, 9, 14, 1, 26, ________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. +9",
                "c. -7",
                "d. +15"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. -15",
        "explanation:"10+0^2=10, 10-1^2=9, 10+2^2=14, 10-3^2=1, 10+4^2=26, 10-5^2=-15 "
        },

         {
            "question": "200, 220, 242, 266.2, 292.82,_______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 324.102",
                "b. 320.102",
                "c. 322.106"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d. 322.102",
        "explanation:"200+10%of200, 220+10%of220, 242+10%of242, 266.2+10%of266.2, 292.82+10%of292.82=322.102"
        },

         {
            "question": "5, 11, 29, 55, 131, __________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 145",
                "c. 150",
                "d. 165"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 181",
        "explanation:"2+2^2-1=5, 3+3^2-1=11, 5+5^2-1=29, 7+7^2-1=55, 11+11^2-1=131, 13+13^2-1=181 ( 2,3,5,7,11,13 are primes ) "
        },

         {
            "question": "6, 12, 30, 56, 132, 182, 306, __________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 370",
                "c. 349",
                "d. 327"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 380",
        "explanation:"2^2+2=6, 3^2+3=12, 5^2+5=30, 7^2+7=56, 11^2+11=132, 13^2+13=182, 17^2+17=306, 19^2+19=380"
        },

         {
            "question": "9, 36, 81, 144, 225, 324, 446",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 225",
                "c. 81",
                "d. 324"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 446",
        "explanation:" 3^2, 6^2, 9^2, 12^2, 15^2, 18^2, 21^2=441"
        },

         {
            "question": "5, 12, 21, 32, 46, 60, 77, 96",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 32",
                "c. 60",
                "d.77"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 46",
        "explanation:" 5×1=5, 6×2=12, 7×3=21, 8×4=32 ,9×5=45"
        },

         {
            "question": "6, 15, 35, 147, 323, 899",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 35",
                "c. 323",
                "d. 899"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a.147",
        "explanation:" Product of Twin Prime numbers
 2×3=6, 3×5=15, 5×7=35, 11×13=143, 17×19=323, 29×31=899"
        },

         {
            "question": "16, 38, 71, 115, 170, 234",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 71",
                "b. 115",
                "c. 170"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d. 234",
        "explanation:"5+11=16, 16+22=38, 38+33=71, 71+44=115, 115+55=170, 170+66=236"
        },

         {
            "question": "50, 50, 75, 150, 375, 1115",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 375",
                "c. 150",
                "d. 75"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 1115",
        "explanation:"100×0.5=50, 50×1=50, 50×1.5=75, 75×2=150, 150×2.5=375, 375×3=1125"
        },

         {
            "question": "10, 12, 16, 24, 40, 72,______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 118",
                "c. 124",
                "d. 112"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a.136",
        "explanation:"Difference between two numbers is 2^n, where n=natural numbers"
        },

         {
            "question": "11, 36, 103, 316, 939,_______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 2648",
                "b. 2048",
                "d. 2126"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c. 2828",
        "explanation:"4×3-1=11, 11×3+3=36, 36×3-5=103, 103×3+7=316, 316×3-9=939, 939×3+11=2828"
        },

         {
            "question": "12, 26, 42, ______, 80, 102",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 56",
                "c. 64",
                "d. 66"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 60",
        "explanation:"1^2+11=12, 2^2+22=26, 3^2+33=42, 4^2+44=60, 5^2+55=80, 6^2+66=102 "
        },

         {
            "question": "6, 18, 72, ________, 2160, 15120",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 340",
                "c. 380",
                "d. 1290"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 360",
        "explanation:"3×2=6, 6×3=18, 18×4=72, 72×5=360, 360×6=2160, 2160×7=15120"
        },
 {
            "question": "3, 7, 13, 21, 31, ________, 57",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 52",
                "c. 49",
                "d. 45"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 43",
        "explanation:"2×1+1=3, 3×2+1=7, 4×3+1=13, 5×4+1=21, 6×5+1=31, 7×6+1=43, 8×7+1=57"
        },


         {
            "question": "3, 13, 31, 57, 91, _______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 121",
                "b. 118",
                "c. 112"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d. 133",
        "explanation:"1^2+2=3, 3^2+4=13, 5^2+6=31, 7^2+8=57, 9^2+10=91, 11^2+12=133"
        },

         {
            "question": "48, 120, 168, 288, 360, _______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 526",
                "c. 512",
                "d. 486"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 528",
        "explanation:"7^2-1=48, 11^2-1=120, 13^2-1=168, 17^2-1=288, 19^2-1=360, 23^2-1=528"
        },

         {
            "question": "429, 924, 635, 536, ________, 927",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 297",
                "b. 972",
                "d. 792"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c. 729",
        "explanation:"Reverse the previous number"
        },

         {
            "question": "32, 53, 75, 117, 1311, 1713, _______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 1719",
                "c. 1715",
                "d. 1921"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 1917",
        "explanation:"Pair of conjugate primes "
        },

         {
            "question": "4, 10, 16, 26, 36 ______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 46",
                "b. 44",
                "d. 52"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c. 50",
        "explanation:"2^2=4, 3^2+1=10, 4^2=16, 5^2+1=26, 6^2=36, 7^2+1=50"
        },

         {
            "question": "112, 100, 76, 64, 40, ______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 24",
                "c. 32",
                "d. 26"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 28",
        "explanation:"19x6-2=112, 17x6-2=100, 13x6-2=76, 11x6-2=64, 7x6-2=40, 5x6-2=28"
        },

         {
            "question": "11, 39, 86, 151, 236, _______",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 331",
                "c. 296",
                "d. 282"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 337",
        "explanation:"3^2+2=11, 6^2+3=39, 9^2+5=86, 12^2+7=151, 15^2+11=236, 18^2+13=337"
        },

         {
            "question": "5, 6, 8, ____, 15, 20, 26",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 13",
                "b. 21",
                "c. 10"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d. 11",
        "explanation:"5, 5+1, 6+2, 8+3, 11+4, 15+5, 20+6"
        },

         {
            "question": "981, 900, 836, 787, ______, 726",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 748",
                "b. 761",
                "d. 746"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c. 751",
        "explanation:"981-9^2=900, 900-8^2=836, 836-7^2=787, 787-6^2=751, 751-5^2=726"
        },

         {
            "question": "5, 8, 9, 8, 5, 0, -7, ________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. -12",
                "c. -11",
                "d. -9"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. -16",
        "explanation:"6x1-1^2=5, 6x2-2^2=8, 6x3-3^2=9, 6x4-4^2=8, 6x5-5^2=5, 6x6-6^2=0, 6x7-7^2=-7, 6x8-8^2=-16"
        },

         {
            "question": "0, 3, 8, 15, 24,________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 31",
                "b. 33",
                "d. 37"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c. 35",
        "explanation:"1^2-1=0, 2^2-1=3, 3^2-1=8, 4^2-1=15, 5^2-1=24, 6^2-1=35"
        },

         {
            "question": "2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21,________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 43",
                "c. 28",
                "d. 57"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 34",
        "explanation:"2+3=5, 3+5=8, 5+8=13, 8+13=21, 13+21=34"
        },

         {
            "question": "100, 89, 82, 77, 74,________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 70",
                "c. 71",
                "d. 68"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 72",
        "explanation:"100-11=89, 89-7=82, 82-5=77, 77-3=74, 74-2=72"
        },

         {
            "question": "0, 6, 24, 60, 120,________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 220",
                "b. 216",
                "d. 206"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "c. 210",
        "explanation:"1^3-1=0, 2^3-2=6, 3^3-3=24, 4^3-4=60, 5^3-5=120, 6^3-6=210"
        },

         {
            "question": "987, 876, 765, 654, 543,________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "b. 324",
                "c. 542",
                "d. 434"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "a. 432",
        "explanation:"Sequence order
                987, 876, 765, 654, 543, 432"
        },

         {
            "question": "2, 6, 18, 54, 162,________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 436",
                "b. 742",
                "c. 438"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d. 486",
        "explanation:"2*3=6, 6*3=18, 18*3=54, 54*3=162, 162*3=486"
        },

         {
            "question": "235, 240, 250, 265, 285, 310,________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 330",
                "b. 320",
                "c. 315"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "d. 340",
        "explanation:"235+5=240, 240+10=250, 250+15=265, 265+20=285, 285+25=310, 310+30=340"
        },

         {
            "question": "82, 65, 50, 37, 26,________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 20",
                "c. 16",
                "d. 18"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 17",
        "explanation:"10*9-8=82, 9*8-7=65, 8*7-6=50, 7*6-5=37, 6*5-4=26, 5*4-3=17"
        },

         {
            "question": "15, 21, 28, 36, 45,________",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 54",
                "c. 56",
                "d. 57"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 55",
        "explanation:"15+6=21, 21+7=28, 28+8=36, 36+9=45, 45+10=55"
        },

         {
            "question": "10, 81, 8, 49, 6, 25,________ , 9",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "a. 16",
                "c. 12",
                "d. 8"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "b. 4",
        "explanation:"10, 9^2, 8, 7^2, 6, 5^2, 4, 3^2"
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },
 {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },

         {
            "question": "",
         "incorrect_answers": [
                "",
                "",
                ""
            ],
            "correct_answer": "",
        "explanation:""
        },


      
      
     
       
       
       
      
    ]
